(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Oh, yeah?
Then what language do I have to speak to this auntie?
Try barking.
But I don't know how to bark.
That's why we could never talk.
Mook! Are you calling me a dog?!
Stop!
I'll finish in just a second.
I do this all the time. Just trust my hands, okay?
Are you almost there?
But there's only one company that seems to stand a chance against us.
Mook's husband's company, right?
If I'd known she'd be this evil,
I wouldn't have let you marry her.
What's past is past, Ma.
Why'd you come home alone? Where's Usa?
I left her in charge at the office.
And did you eat yet, son?
Yes, Ma. I should go get some rest.
Where are you going?
I'm leaving Kuk,
and I'm taking Kongkwan home to live with my mom.
Oh well,
you're such a workaholic that you neglect your family.
No man could tolerate that.
So he had to cheat on his wife,
who's working hard to build a life, Ma?
If you really think he's in the right,
then I've got nothing to say to you.
If you think you can make it alone, go ahead.
We'll see about that.
Just make sure you leave empty-handed.
The company belongs to Kuk.
Don't you worry.
My daughter and I will leave empty-handed.
And I'll show you just how far I can go.
As for the company,
let's just say I did you a favor.
I hope you'll take good care of it.
Because one day,
we might become rivals.
You'll never defeat a dragon like Kuk.
Damn you, Mook.
HOTEL RESERVATION FORMS LIST OF HOTELS
KRABI
Tawan, let's eat.
Here.
No. I want to wait for Mom.
Why isn't she home yet, Saifah?
She said she'd go shopping for a bit.
She'll be back soon.
Come on, let's eat.
A Round Trip Travel has submitted their program, Mr. Thee.
They sure work fast.
Please email it to me.
It's quite late, Mr. Thee.
Why don't you do it tomorrow?
It's alright.
I want to see if I like their program.
Sure, sir.
Where on earth did I put my towel?
Really, Mook?! I'm going to be a father?
I'm so happy.
Mook, let's go tell Ma. She'd be so happy.
I have a meeting with a client today to finalize the group tour.
How about we go tell her together once the meeting's over?
Please?
Fine.
Look.
What's up?
Mook.
It's late. You're still up?
You can go to bed.
I need to send our client a quotation.
The wrap-up meeting's tomorrow.
Just sleep first.
Wait, Kuk! You moved everything!
Can you leave me alone? Can't you see I'm working?
Kuk.
I… Kuk.
It's just my pregnancy hormones.
Kuk!
Okay, so we'll go over two groups today.
I like the design, but I think the color could be changed a bit.
Let's not go home till we're drunk!
Let's go all out!
What's up, sweetie?
She's sleeping so soundly, Mook.
Look at her face.
- I wonder who she looks like. - Her father, of course!
She does look like you, a little bit.
Of course, the daughter would look like her dad,
- right, honey? - Right?
- Look at her. - Her cheeks are so red.
What's up, honey?
She's sleeping so soundly.
Come on. Cheers!
Are you having fun?
Yes.
Cheers.
Why does Mook
treat me like I don't matter?
I understand.
She has a good man like you by her side,
yet she's taking you for granted.
What are you doing?
Do you still miss your family?
What?
Did seeing her face again make you miss her that bad?
Usa, that's not it.
I just happened to find the rubber duck when I opened the drawer.
Then we're good.
Don't you dare think about going back to Mook.
Everything fine at work?
Yes, it is.
I planned with the team to use this project
to promote our business.
Don't you worry, Kuk.
We'll surely win against Mook on this one.
Oh, Usa.
Where did you put my towel?
I'll go find it for you.
WAT PAKNAM BHASICHAROEN
If you're working this hard, I'm sure we'll win.
But for now, you should go home and rest, Mook.
You'll be hearing good news tomorrow.
I guarantee you!
Okay. I trust your skills, Mook.
We should grab some food before you go home.
How about some late night rice soup?
- Deal. - Okay, let's go!
Just a moment.
- Can I help you? - Sure.
- Can I put this away? - Yes, please.
YOU HAVE A NEW EMAIL
- It's here! - It's here! The email!
We got the email! We got the email!
We got the email!
Please calm down.
- Hey! - Mook!
- Mook, get over here! They just replied. - Come here!
Really, Boss?
Let me see.
- Should I open it now? - Yeah!
Is this a sick joke?
Did we lose, Mook?
Where are you going?
To The One.
Mook!
‪The heck? Boss!
- His office, right? - Uh, wait.
- Please wait a moment! - I need to see Mr. Thee now!
- Let me tell him first! - No!
Please calm--
It's alright, Mr. Pitak.
I'd like to know why you changed my company's entire tour program.
It's all just to test
your company's ability to handle
and solve immediate problems
or unforeseen circumstances.
If you can't do it, then it's over.
I'll choose your rival company.
So?
If you changed the program to test my company's professionalism,
then I'm happy to oblige.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
I'd like to pick the guide for this trip.
The guide for this trip has to be you only.
How unlucky can I get?
Oh, Mook!
What a coincidence.
Are you here to see Mr. Thee too?
That's none of your business.
Why should I tell you?
Afraid of losing?
Is that why you came to see him in private?
I'd never do stupid things like that.
But I don't doubt you would.
I just came to welcome him officially.
It's common courtesy.
You wouldn't get it.
It's because I use my brain to work, rather than…
using my cleavage, like you do.
Let me guess.
Family Tour and Travel probably hasn't submitted anything for The One's task,
so you came looking for a shortcut.
It doesn't matter what I use to work.
Come to think of it,
I won against you once.
This time is no different.
Mr. Thee will surely choose me too.
I'm glad you're so confident.
Just do your best,
so I won't have to watch the company I built fall apart.
Why isn't it done yet?
And where's Usa?
I asked you where she is!
She said she's going to The One.
Why?
I'm not sure.
Hurry and get it done.
Submit it to The One before A Round Trip Travel does. Got it?
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
USA
Yesterday we had a briefing, so I didn't get to talk to you.
And I wanted to officially welcome you again today
and also introduce myself.
Family Tour and Travel is looking forward to working with The One.
You really shouldn't have.
Submitting your work would've sufficed.
Mr. Thee isn't very good with formalities.
If that is all, I’ll take my leave.
Pleased to meet you.
Submitting your plan earlier
would've been nicer than that gift basket.
Sure.
I'll submit it for your consideration soon.
Mr. Thee is just straightforward.
I hope you don't mind.
Not at all.
I understand.
I like a challenge anyway.
So why exactly did Mr. Thee change your entire program?
To get back at me, of course.
What do you mean? I don't get it.
The guy who asked for laundry fees after I threw up on him is him.
Is that true, Mook?
It might sound like a coincidence,
but it's true.
It just so happens that he's rich, he's our client,
and we want this project, is all.
If that's the case, he may be biased against us.
If you feel uncomfortable, we can skip this project
and look for a new one.
No way, Boss.
I'll prove to him that silly pranks like that
do not work on me.
Don't worry, Boss.
I'll win this deal for our company, no matter what.
HOW ABOUT AT THE COMPANY? THAI DESSERTS THAI MASSAGE, DONATION AT ORPHANAGE
If you're changing everything,
why not choose the locations in the first place?
LIST OF DESTINATIONS
ORPHANAGE, HOST CLUB
SILOM, NANA, THAI DESSERT SHOP
HOST CLUB
I knew it!
I'm gonna teach you a lesson, kid.
Kongkwan, I need to see Khim and Ploy tonight.
Just go to bed with Grandma, honey.
I'll give you a kiss once I'm home.
Don't drink, Mommy. Don't drink and drive.
Roger that. Mommy won't drink for sure. Don't worry.
Good night, honey. Mwah.
The joys of being a family woman.
Gotta call them everywhere you go.
Unlike me.
I'm so free.
I never have to call anyone when I go out.
Sounds like you've got nobody.
Or maybe you can't choose who to call yet.
You know me too well.
Why isn't Ploy here yet?
It's not unlike her to be late.
- Am I right? - Yeah.
- Let's just eat it all. - Can you reach it?
Sorry, guys.
My work wasn't done yet, and it’s year-end closing time.
- Oh, boy. - Watch your skirt.
I need to breathe.
Yeah. Catch your breath.
Okay.
This is all you ordered?
That's not nearly enough!
I'm starving to death here. Can I order some more?
Suit yourself.
- I'm just so hungry. - Sure.
Mook,
I heard your company's pitching for the big project too?
If we land this deal, it'll keep us afloat for a while.
I don't care about that.
I only care about the CEO, who's apparently a total stud.
Well, did you also hear that he's a total jerk?
He's so snarky too.
It won't be easy.
I'm up against Family Tour and Travel too.
Against Kuk, you mean?
Can he just burn in hell already?
When will he leave you alone?
Please don't be mad at me, Kuk.
I only did it for our company.
If we're on Mr. Thee's good side, things will be easier.
Can you swear on your life
what you did was only for our work?
Even Mook went to see him too.
If I hadn't gone, we'd be at a disadvantage.
You're too naive to keep up with her schemes.
Why did she go see him anyway?
Do you really have to ask?
These days, you need to pull strings to do well in business.
Seeing him in private like that…
She must be scheming something.
As for Mr. Thee,
I'm sure I can handle him. Mark my words.
I'll beat Mook, no matter what.
I won't let her call you a loser.
Thank you, Usa, for doing all this for me.
Let's go.
I just don't get it.
You've broken up.
Why can't he mind his own business?
I think he's pitching against you on purpose.
And why do you care, Khim?
I don't see Mook complaining one bit.
Let's stop talking about others.
It'll only bring us down.
Hey, I have something important to tell you.
But really, though,
he caused all kinds of problems while you were together.
Now you've broken up, yet he's still at it.
Speak of the devil.
So many coincidences today, Mook.
Yeah, what a coincidence.
Speak of the devil and he appears.
- Who are you calling the devil? - Usa.
Go ahead, then.
You hit me, I hit you back. Fair game.
Idam me ñātinam hotu, sukhitā hontu ñātayo
There, I've forgiven you.
May you rest in peace.
‪Hey, Mook!
Would you stop it, Mook?
Stop acting this way.
This is exactly why we could never talk!
So I have to be like her?
Is that how you can talk?
Also, there's no need for us to talk anyway.
- Mook! - What?!
Excuse me. Please don't fight.
Please lower your voice.
You're bothering others.
Usa, let's leave.
My apologies.
I'll have someone clean up the broken bowl.
Thank you.
You okay, Mook?
I've lost my appetite. My mood's ruined.
Why'd we have to meet them?
It tastes great, though.
Look at you. What a mess!
Here.
You're acting like Kongkwan.
- Let me wipe it off. - Like Kongkwan? Your daughter?
Keep it.
- Keep it in case you need it. - Mook.
Are you okay, Mook?
Ever since the day I found them together at a hotel,
I've always told myself
I'm no one important to Kuk anymore.
For me,
my love life has zero hope, and marriage is hell.
Here, an invitation to my wedding!
- Wedding?! - Wedding?!
I'm getting married.
My name?
Who is it?
"Udom"?
Who's that? You never mentioned him.
He's the son of my dad's best friend.
When did you two start dating?
How come we never knew?
I've never met him either.
I met him once when my brother was little.
On a Chinese New Year.
Wait a second.
Are you telling me it's an arranged marriage?
In this day and age?!
I used to believe in love too,
but see what happened to Mook.
He and she loved each other since college.
He was her first boyfriend.
They got married, had a kid, started a family,
built a fortune together and everything.
Yet still, they broke up.
Whether we love each other or not, and whether it's arranged or not,
in the end, there's no guarantee if your love life will fail or not.
But if you need to marry someone you don't love,
who you didn't choose,
and without getting to know each other, that can't be good, right?
Love needs to come from the heart.
Think this through, Ploy.
We'll probably end up loving each other after a while.
Sometimes love life is just like buying lottery tickets.
You know what?
Come on.
Here's to Ploy and her wedding.
I hope you win the jackpot in the lottery, my friend.
Hey, Khim! Come on!
Fine.
Whatever works for you, works for me.
Congrats, girl.
I'm glad to have you both as my friends.
Thank you, you two.
Cheers.
- Yay! - Yay!
Mr. Thee.
What's the matter, Mr. Thee?
This is exactly why
- we could never talk! - That's Ms. Mook
- So I have to be… - and
Mr. Apichart, the CEO of Family Tour and Travel?
Is it some kind of bad blood?
Looks like they had a fight at a restaurant.
Well,
they're probably business rivals.
After all, they work in the same industry, Mr. Thee.
I want to learn about their past,
see if they've got bad blood.
I just want to be aware before I decide to work with them.
Of course. I'll look into it for you.
And Family Tour and Travel's submitted their program.
I emailed it to you.
Then, I'll start testing the program and services
of A Round Trip Travel first.
Please let them know.
Sure, sir.
That's your new outfit, May?
Isn't it cute?
Yeah.
I'm going to see a client, so I need a good first impression.
That's true.
- Are you impressed? - Super.
- You like it? - Yes.
Mook, here's some coffee.
Black coffee. Less sweet, but still sweet.
- Thank you. - Of course.
Is everything prepared?
Yes. I've coordinated with all the teams in the area.
- Good work. I'd better get going. - Sure.
- Bye-- - Wait!
I forgot to tell you.
I'd like to pick the guide for this trip.
The guide for this trip has to be you only.
Let's go.
May, you don't have to go. I'll go alone.
Come on!
I… bought a new outfit just for this job! I'm so ready.
Well… I want you to stay here with Whan
and help collaborate about the locations from this office.
‪Please.
Mook, will you really be fine on your own?
Of course! I'll show them who's boss.
I'm going now. Bye.
Mook.
You got this!
- I got this! - Good luck!
Okay, bye.
I'll have this, then. Can you make a new one?
Good morning, Mr. Pitak.
Good morning, Ms. Mook.
This way, please.
I'm not coming. Mr. Thee will go alone.
And where is he?
Good morning, Mr. Thee.
This way, please.
No. I'm going in my car.
You can drive, right?
I can, but I--
It's fine.
I found a driver for the day. You can take a rest.
Excuse me.
Can I cancel your service for today? You can leave.
- Sure, ma'am. - I'll handle the payment later.
May I grab my stuff?
Thank you. I'm very sorry.
Oh, Mr. Thee.
You aren't letting her off easy, are you?
Mr. Thee, this angle's perfect.
Let me take a picture for you.
One…
Wat Saket was originally known as Wat Sakae.
It's an ancient temple originated in the Ayutthaya era.
During King Rama I's reign,
His Majesty ordered its renovation and the excavation of a canal around it,
then renamed it
to Wat Saket, which means "to wash one's hair."
And here's a view of the temple grounds.
That's called the Phu Khao Thong, or the Golden Mount,
which…
is a pagoda built on top of a man-made hill.
Mr. Thee.
Mr. Thee, please take an umbrella.
Why don't you open it?
Mr. Thee, please wait!
Please be careful. Mr. Thee!
Mr. Thee,
please be careful.
Please go ahead, Mr. Thee.
Go on ahead.
There's also a rest stop up ahead which is their coffee shop, Mr. Thee.
I haven't mentioned, but the stairs have 144 steps,
and you can…
You can also ring the bells, Mr. Thee.
Want to try it?
Please go right ahead.
Would you like a picture?
Mr. Thee,
from this angle, if you stop here, you'll get a full view of Bangkok.
And that is the Loha Prasat…
Mr. Thee!
Mr. Thee, from this angle,
you can get a full view of the surroundings,
and more importantly, a view of Bangkok.
There's Pratunam.
And there's also the Bobae Market.
They're both wholesale hubs that many foreigners love.
Mr. Thee… Mr. Thee!
This angle's perfect.
Let me take a picture for you.
One, two, thre…
During King Rama IV's reign,
Phu Khao Thong was later renamed to Borommabanphot.
At the top, the Buddha's relics are enshrined inside.
You may head up there and pay your respects.
No need to take off your shoes, Mr. Thee. Be careful.
Isn't he tired at all?
Here are the flowers, incense, and candles.
There are many types of tungs.
The one I hung just now is a tung of the 12 star signs,
or the 12 zodiac signs,
which is made of saa paper, with the 12 zodiac signs printed on it.
It is believed that by offering a tung,
you bring blessings to yourself and your family.
And these are called Lanna lanterns.
It is believed that
they can bring blessings and light to your family.
BREWED COFFEE SHOP
Excuse me.
Can you buy some of my snacks?
Let's see. What do we have here?
I'll have this one, then.
Here you go.
I don't have change.
That's alright.
Keep the change and treat yourself with meals and snacks.
Thank you.
Mr. Thee, here's your iced coffee.
Let's hurry. We've got two more stops.
What about your coffee?
Mr. Thee, please wait!
Mr. Thee!
Of course.
Our team at Family Tour will do our best.
Yes.
Thank you.
Usa,
we won, right?
Not yet.
Mr. Pitak just told me Mr. Thee's got the program we sent.
Mr. Thee will set up a date for us to take him on our program's tour
to assess us and decide.
Why are there so many steps?
He should be able to decide just with our company name alone.
According to Mr. Pitak,
A Round Trip Travel had to do the same.
Don't worry, Kuk.
I'll take good care of Mr. Thee.
I won't let Mook win.
PIAMSUK ORPHANAGE
Here!
Why did you want to come here?
Mr. Thee.
Just to let you know, I only did the basic arrangements.
I didn't ask for a formal welcome or a ceremony
because I know you like to keep it private,
and you don't like a big fuss.
Great customer analysis.
Wait in the car.
I'm sorry?
Didn't you just tell me I don't like a big fuss?
But I'm your guide.
For this place, no guide is needed.
So you brought me along, for what?
- Thee! - Hello. What about the others?
- They're inside. - Let's go.
You're too kind, Mrs. Prao.
You've always got a gift for us.
I never saw you up close before.
You're as pretty as all the moms said.
My family happens to know the CEO of that place.
You can take your kids there for a vacation.
I will.
Uh, didn't Mr. Anapat come with you today?
Well, work's quite busy for him lately.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but I suggest you come here more often.
That way, the other parents can understand who's who.
I didn't want to tell you this,
but there's a mom who likes to act
as if she wants to be Poonpun's mom too.
And who's that?
Well, it's Mook, Kongkwan's mom, of course.
It's true! That woman acts overly familiar with Poonpun's dad.
It's probably nothing.
She's the manager at Pat's company.
It won't be easy for her,
even if she wants to be more than that.
Pat has standards, you know.
Grandma!
- Hello, Grandma. - Mommy's got work today,
so I came to pick you up.
- Are you hungry? - Yes, I am!
I made a bunch of food for you. Let's go.
You'll get to ride it soon.
See? See?
Wonderful.
- Okay. - Yay!
- I'll bring it there. - Go try it.
Who's going to ride it?
- Go do a test-ride. - Ride it! Ride it!
- Try it. - Let's go.
Careful, okay?
Three, two, one.
Can I talk to you for a bit?
Sure.
What's up, Whan?
I finished arranging the special program for tonight.
The client will be pleased for sure.
Great work. Can you guys stay on standby?
Just in case something happens.
Our client's so bipolar. So unpredictable.
Okay!
Thank you.
Come on in, Mr. Thee.
I prepared a special show for you.
I'm sure you'll be impressed.
Are you shy?
I understand.
You must not get to go out in the way that you want so often.
So, enjoy yourself. I'll be outside, so you won't feel uncomfortable.
Where are you going?
I'll be waiting at a coffee shop nearby.
You can stay here as long as you'd like.
It's fine. You don't have to wait.
We'll go in together.
Mr. Thee. Hey!
Oh, hey! I'm here, sis.
Ooh, he's so hot!
Do you have a reservation?
Uh, for A Round Trip Travel.
All done. I booked a table and put it on the program.
Thank you. Let's see.
Mook.
Um… Is Mr. Thee…
You know, is he really… that type of guy?
I don't know either,
but this is what the client's requested, so we must oblige.
Our client may be picky, snarky,
and not so good with people,
but we need to prove our company's professionalism to him.
Got it.
Oh, Whan,
I want to include something special to impress him.
- Special… - Got any ideas?
This place hosts a special show for VIP guests.
I booked the show already.
Once Mr. Thee's done watching the show,
he'll definitely sign a contract with us.
Perfect.
Then I want it to be very special.
Go all out.
You got it, Mook.
VIP lounge and a special show…
Upstairs, please.
Go ahead, Mr. Thee.
You've never been here?
Why would a woman like me come here?
And I thought you knew it all.
Here we go.
Not me!
Alright. Long show, huh?
‪Thank you.
Thank you, Thee. It's been a while.
You know him?
Tony used to study abroad with me,
but he prefers this life, so he came back to work in Thailand.
That's why you chose this place.
I even asked Tony to put on a very special show for you.
I can't believe you.
Let's go home. I had a lot of fun today.
Mr. Thee!
Well, aren't you cute?
Are you single?
Hey, excuse me.
What?
- Are you crazy? - What?
What was that?
You better go find your face
- 'cause girl, you lost it. - How embarrassing.
Mr. Thee,
- why did you do that? - Do what?
What? Well, what'd you kiss me for?
The situation called for it.
If I didn't kiss you, that person would've kissed me.
And if I had to choose, I'd rather kiss an auntie like you.
Auntie?
You're calling me an auntie?
What else should I call you?
Mook. Ms. Mook.
Sister Mook. Anything.
You brought me here,
so you're responsible for any danger I may face.
Isn't that the duty of a good guide,
Auntie Mook?
Please dress appropriately.
Show some respect for the place and for me.
I'm so sorry.
Have we met before?
Don't leave me.
Boss. Boss--
Boss!
How could you do this, Mr. Thee?
You're not a gentleman!
What are you talking about?
Subtitle translation by: Ramil Natnitiwitaya